Model Designer 12.1 New Function
Drag the background image into the background
The image can be added to the 2D window background from the resource manager
as a background image
Use the shortcut to switch window layout
Press the LW key to zoom in on the selected window
Press LW again to return to the original layout
Display statistics
You can view all kinds of information related to clothing through the display statistics
Please view our operation manual to get more information
Combine with the USD file Omniverse Connector
Through USD, you can improve the cooperation efficiency with multiple 3D software
Add more data to the platform
By using the USD file format, data interaction is achieved on the Omniverse platform
The cooperation process becomes smoother and faster
Thank you for watching